Guide to the Fred Chappell Papers, 1944-2019 and undated RL.00213
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings by Chappell Series, 1960-1997 and undated
  - Essays Subseries, ca. 1960-1997 and undated
    - Individual essays, in alphabetical order:
      - First Night Come Round Again, undated, rec'd 1997 July (Box WE-1)
      - Foreword to Eugene Grace poetry collection, undated, rec'd 1989 June (Box WE-1)
      - Foreword to Kelly Cherry poetry collection, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - ca. 1960-1969 ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Foreword to Steve Lautermilch's The Little Hours, undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WE-1)
      - Foreword to the O. Henry Prize, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Foreword to Tom Huey's Force hymn, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Function of the Poet, undated, rec'd July 1990 (Box WE-1)
      - Gay Wilson Allen, undated (Box WE-1)
      - Georgicorum, undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WE-1)
      - Gibbons Ruark, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WE-1)
      - The Good Songs Behind Us: Southern Fiction of the 1990s, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WE-1)
      - Hiram Haydn's Latest Report, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Houyhnhnm, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Ignorant Assets, undated, rec'd 1987 July (Box WE-1)
      - 'I'm in the Racket': Carolyn Kizer's Poetry, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Image of the South in Film, ca. 1960-1969 (2 items) (Box WE-1)
      - In Progress, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Indivisible Presence of Randall Jarrell, undated (Box WE-1)
      - Interview with Stuart Wright, 1991 July 22 (Box WE-1)
      - Introduction to New North Carolina Poetry, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Kerouac: New Version, undated, rec'd 1995 June (Box WE-1)
      - A Lacking Middle, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Lion Tamer: George Garrett's Short Stories, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Longing to Belong, undated, rec'd 1987 July (Box WE-1)
      - Matthew Prior: A Stoic Moment, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - 'Menfolks Are Heathens,' ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - 'A Million Million Suns': Poetry and Science, undated, rec'd 1997 July (Box WE-1)
      - Modernity in Western Art, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Modesty and Honesty, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Moon, 1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Mountain Trout Fishing, ca. 1960-1969 (4 items) (Box WE-1)
      - Movie Essay, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Music of 'Each in His Season,' 1995 July (Box WE-1)
      - A Newly Necessary Prospect, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - 'Not as a Leaf': Southern Poetry and the Innovation of Tradition, undated, rec'd 1997 July (Box WE-1)
      - The Novels of Sylvia Wilkinson, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Old and the Odd, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - On the Teaching of Writing, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Open Book, undated, rec'd 1995 June (Box WE-1)
      - Paris (2 items), undated, rec'd 1995 June (Box WE-1)
      - Peter Taylor: the Genial Mentor, 1996 Feb. (Box WE-1)
      - Piecework: the Longer Poem Returns, ca. 1996 July (Box WE-1)
      - The Poet, the Children of Ferocity, and Cricket, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Poet's Garden, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WE-1)
      - The Poetry of Clarity, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Powers of Observation: the Stone, the Hawk, the Solitary I, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WE-1)
      - Pre-Season Ramblings, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Preface, ca. 1960-1969 (2 items) (Box WE-1)
      - Propositions about Literature and History, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - A Quirky Little Anthology of Appalachian Poetry, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Rape of the Lock: Some Metrical Considerations, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Rediscovering the Necessary, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Sardonic Imagination: Allen Tate's 'The Fathers,' undated, rec'd July 1990 (2 items) (Box WE-1)
      - Science and the Artist's Vision, ca. 1960-1969 (2 items) (Box WE-1)
      - The S-F Film Image, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Skin Flicks, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - The Stranger in the Mirror: George Garrett's Tragical History Players (2 items), undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WE-1)
      - The Surface of Earth: A Pavement [?] of Good Intentions, ca. 1975 (Box WE-1)
      - Taking Measures: Violent Intruders in William Hoffman's Short Fiction, undated, rec'd 1997 July (Box WE-1)
      - Talking Out of Doors, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Teacher, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Thanks But No Thanks, undated, rec'd 1997 July (Box WE-1)
      - The Unrevealing Revelation: Alan Cheuse's Short Stories, ca. 1990 (Box WE-1)
      - What Did Adrian Leverkuhn Create? undated, rec'd 1986 June (Box WE-1)
      - The Worlds That Could Be Ours, undated, rec'd 1993 July (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay on Eve Shelnutt's The Love Child, ca. 1979 (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay on film, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay on 'folk artists,' ca. 1970-1979 (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay on Tennyson, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay on young writers, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WE-1)
      - Untitled essay, undated (Box WE-1)
  - Reviews Subseries, ca. 1970-1997 and undated
    Arranged alphabetically by title reviewed. Certain longer reviews appear in the Essays Subseries as well as in the collection listed there, Plow Naked. Versions may also appear in the Notebooks Subseries.
    - The Accidental Tourist, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - After Borges, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Audubon, A Vision ca. 1960-1969 (Box WR-1)
    - Augusta Played, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Bardana Creek, et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - Balancing on Stones, undated (Box WR-1)
    - A Beast in View, et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - Beasts of the Southern Wilds and Other Stories, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Best American Essays 1987, undated, rec'd June 1989 (Box WR-1)
    - Bone of My Bones, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Caesarion, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Cale, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Celestial Navigation, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Chasing Dad, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Clan Anderson, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Collected Poems: 1957-1982 (Wendell Berry), undated (Box WR-1)
    - Collected Poems: 1982-1985 (Stephen Spender), undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - The Collected Poems of Octavio Paz 1957-1987, The Collected Poems of Octavio Paz 1957-1987, undated, rec'd June 1989 (Box WR-1)
    - Confessions of Chembino, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Dara Win, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Deaths of Animals and Lesser Gods, et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - Departing as Ain, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Don't Look Back, undated, rec'd July 1987 (Box WR-1)
    - Edgar Rice Burroughs: The Man Who Created Tarzan, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Enderby's Dark Lady, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Entered from the Sun, undated, rec'd July 1991 (Box WR-1)
    - An Evening Performance: New and Selected Short Stories, et. al., (3 versions) undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Every Poet in His Humor, undated, rec'd June 1992 (Box WR-1)
    - Expedition to Earth, et. al., ca. 1960-1969 (Box WR-1)
    - Familiar Ground, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Family Time (2 versions), undated (Box WR-1)
    - The First Man, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The First Man on the Sun, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Five New Southern Women Poets, undated (Box WR-1)
    - A Green Place, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Gregg Press Science Fiction Series, Things to Come et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - Hammertown Tales, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Here to Get My Baby Out of Jail, undated (Box WR-1)
    - A Historical and Critical Survey of the Science-Fiction Film, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Hudson Review, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Irish Erotic Art (2 versions), undated (Box WR-1)
    - Irony in the Mind's Life, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Keaton: The Man Who Wouldn't Lie Down, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Laurel Review, issue of Winter 1981, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Laurel and Thorn: The Athlete in American Literature, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Learning the Mother Tongue, et. al., undated, rec'd June 1989 (Box WR-1)
    - The Light as They Found It, undated, rec'd July 1991 (Box WR-1)
    - Lives of X, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Long Approach, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Looking Backward: T. L. Sherred's "Cue for Quiet," undated, rec'd July 1995 (Box WR-1)
    - The Lost America of Love, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Love I, the Crooked Thing, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Lovecraft, A Biography, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Loving a Woman in Two Worlds, et. al., undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Maiden Voyages and Their Pilots, undated, rec'd July 1993 (Box WR-1)
    - The Man Who Named the McPoem, undated, rec'd July 1993 (Box WR-1)
    - The Medicine Woman, et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - Meeting in Infinity, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Midnight Was My Cry, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Midquest, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Mr. Palomar, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Montale's Reactionary Revolution, undated, rec'd July 1995 (Box WR-1)
    - The News from Ireland and Other Stories, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - North Carolina's 400 Years: Signs Along the Way, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Off for the Sweet Hereafter, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Once in Europa, undated, rec'd July 1987 (Box WR-1)
    - One Is A Wanderer, undated rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Open Letter to Robert Morgan, ca. 1960-1969 (Box WR-1)
    - Past Master, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Pianoplayers, undated, rec'd July 1987 (Box WR-1)
    - The Poetry of Randall Jarrell, undated undated (Box WR-1)
    - Poetry of the World Wars, undated, rec'd July 1991 (Box WR-1)
    - Portrait of Reader Reading, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - The Ragged Way People Fall Out of Love, et. al., June 14, 1991 (Box WR-1)
    - Randall Jarrell's Letters, (2 versions) undated (Box WR-1)
    - Red Clay Reader, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Red Owl, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Restless Water, undated (Box WR-1)
    - The Sacrifice, et. al., undated (Box WR-1)
    - A Season of Loss, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - Seizures of the Sun, undated, rec'd July 1997 (Box WR-1)
    - Slammer, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Spirits, undated, rec'd June 1989 (Box WR-1)
    - South Dakota Review, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Statues, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Still, Sad Music, undated, rec'd July 1993 (Box WR-1)
    - Success Stories, undated, rec'd July 1987 (Box WR-1)
    - The Surface of Earth, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Tennessee Writers, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Three Books of Poems, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Traffic, With Ghosts, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Transformations, undated (Box WR-1)
    - Ulysses: The Corrected Text, undated, rec'd July 1987 (Box WR-1)
    - W. B. Yeats, A New Biography, undated (Box WR-1)
    - W. H. Auden: A Tribute, undated (Box WR-1)
    - White Monkeys, undated (Box WR-1)
    - White Well of Spain: The Mysteries of Andalusian Culture, undated, rec'd June 1986 (Box WR-1)
    - William Trowbridge, Heather Ross Miller, and Brian Swann, undated (Box WR-1)
  - Notebooks Subseries, ca. 1960-1997 and undated
    Arranged chronologically to the extent possible; since most of Chappell's work is undated, the sequence is necessarily arbitrary at many points. Sometimes drafts of correspondence in the notebooks provide clues to the general time span of the notebook. For bibliographic reference purposes, each notebook is numbered in brackets in the top right of the first page (not the cover). If the date the Library received the notebook is known, that is also recorded here.
    - 29 folders (Box WN-1)
    - 30 folders (Box WN-2)
    - 31 folders (Box WN-3)
    - 6 folders (Box WN-4)
  - Miscellaneous Subseries, ca. 1960-1997 and undated
    Miscellaneous writings arranged alphabetically by category, then alphabetically by title within categories unless otherwise noted. Includes genres in which Chappell has written only a few works, such as plays; speeches and addresses; an autobiography; and various notes and fragments.
    - Autobiography, undated rec'd June 1986 (Box WM-1)
    - Blurbs and recommendations (Box WM-1)
    - Notes and Fragments, ca. 1960-1997 and undated, 5 folders (Box WM-1)
    - Plays: translation of Euripides' Alcestis, 2 folders (Box WM-1)
    - Plays: Asses Galore, being the Asinaria of the renowned Roman dramatist, Plautus, as translated and adapted by Fred Chappell (Box WM-1)
    - Plays: Moonjox, 3 folders (Box WM-1)
    - Plays: fragments (Box WM-1)
    - Speeches and Addresses, 4 folders (Box WM-1)
- Printed Material Series, 1955-1997 and undated
  Consists primarily of serials containing writings by Chappell, arranged in the following genre subseries: Fiction, Poetry, Essays, Reviews, Speeches and Addresses, and Miscellaneous.
  - Fiction Subseries, 1956-1997 and undated
    Serials containing stories and novel excerpts by Chappell, arranged chronologically.
    - 1956 (Box PF-1)
      - The Archive, Vol. 68, No. 3, Feb.: The Second Coming (Box PF-1)
    - 1962
      - The Archive, Vol. 74, No. 3, Apr.: For the Time, Being: Two (Box PF-1)
      - The Archive, Vol. 74, No. 4, May: The Golden Hook (chapter 3 of a novel) (Box PF-1)
    - 1963
      - The Sewanee Review, Vol. LXXI, No. 2, Spring: For the Time, Being (Box PF-1)
    - 1964
      - Saturday Evening Post, May 9: A Property of Hope. See Oversize Material (Box PF-1)
    - 1968
      - La Nouvelle Revue Française, Vol. 16, No. 190, Oct. 1: Héritage (traduction de Michel Gresset) (Box PF-1)
    - 1969
      - UNCG Alumni News, Vol. 57, No. 3, Spring: Gimlet (excerpt from a novel) (Box PF-1)
    - 1970
      - North Carolina Folklore, Vol. XVIII, No. 2, May: Elmer and Buford (Box PF-1)
    - 1974
      - Graffiti, No. 2, Spring: Judas (Box PF-1)
    - 1975
      - Appalachian Heritage, Vol. 3, No. 3, Summer: Duet (Box PF-1)
    - 1976
      - Francis Marion Review, Vol. I, No. 2: Indiscretions (Box PF-1)
      - The North Carolina Review, Winter: Broken Blossoms (Box PF-1)
    - 1977
      - The Carolina Quarterly, Vol. XXIX, No. 3, Fall: The Three Boxes (Box PF-1)
      - Columbia: A Magazine of Poetry and Prose, Fall: Anna (Box PF-1)
    - 1978
      - Light Years: Mrs. Franklin Ascends (Box PF-1)
      - Appalachian Heritage, Vol. 6, No. 1, Winter: A Penance on Ember Mountain (Box PF-1)
      - New Mexico Humanities Review, Vol. 1, No. 2, May: Children of Strikers (Box PF-1)
      - Florists' Review, Vol. 162, No. 4197, May 11: Linnaeus Forgets (Box PF-1)
    - 1979
      - Appalachian Writers: excerpts from The Gaudy Place, My Grandmother Washes Her Feet (poem), and My Grandmother Washes Her Vessels (poem) (Box PF-1)
      - Tar Heel, Vol. VII, No. 1, Jan./Feb.: Blackbeard's Shadow (Box PF-1)
      - The Georgia Review, Vol. XXXIII, No. 1, Spring: Moments of Light (Box PF-1)
      - The Greensboro Sun, Vol. 7, Issue 2, Apr. 1: Notes Toward a Theory of Flight (Box PF-1)
    - 1980
      - Black Warrior Review, Vol. 6, No. 2, Spring: The Admirer (Box PF-1)
      - New Mexico Humanities Review, Vol. 3, No. 1, Spring: The Shadow Thief (Box PF-1)
      - The Arts Journal, Vol. 5, No. 8, May: The Watch (Box PF-1)
      - Long Pond Review, 7: A Mountain Ghost (Box PF-1)
      - Cold Mountain Review, Vol. 9, Spring: Miss Prue (Box PF-1)
      - The Akros Review, No. 5, Fall: Ladies from Lapland (Box PF-1)
      - The Georgia Review, Vol. XXXV, No. 4, Winter: The Snow That Is Nothing In the Triangle (Box PF-1)
      - Quarterly West, No. 13, Fall/Winter: Things Beyond Us (Box PF-1)
    - 1982
      - Pembroke Magazine, No. 14: Slap (Box PF-1)
      - Writer's Forum, Vol. 8: The Furlough (Box PF-1)
      - Xavier Review, Vol. 2, No. 1 and 2: Enough (Box PF-1)
      - New Mexico Humanities Review, Vol. 5, No. 1, Spring: The Dreaming Orchid (Box PF-1)
    - 1983
      - La Nouvelle Revue Francaise: Les Enfantes de Fibreville (Box PF-1)
      - The Literary Review, Vol. 26, No. 3, Spring: The Maker of One Coffin (Box PF-1)
      - The Crescent Review, No. 2, Fall: A Woman One Time (Box PF-1)
      - Memphis State Review, Vol. 4, No. 1, Fall: Blood Shadow (Box PF-1)
      - TriQuarterly 58, Fall: The Storytellers (Box PF-1)
      - South Dakota Review, Vol. 21, No. 3, Autumn: The Change of Heart (Box PF-2)
    - 1984
      - The Missouri Review, Vol. VII, No. 3: The Posse (Box PF-2)
      - The Chattahoochee Review, Vol. IV, No. 2, Winter: The Good Time and The Story (poem) (Box PF-2)
      - The Chattahoochee Review, Vol. IV, No. 3, Spring: Barcarole (Box PF-2)
      - The Texas Review, Vol. V, No. 1 and 2, Spring/Summer: Weird Tales (Box PF-2)
      - The Chariton Review, Vol. 10, No. 2, Fall: Bright Star of a Summer Evening (Box PF-2)
    - 1985
      - TriQuarterly 20: Twentieth Anniversary, No. 63: The Storytellers (Box PF-2)
      - The South Atlantic Quarterly, Vol. 84, No. 1, Winter: First Night Once More (Box PF-2)
      - Denver Quarterly, Vol. 20, No. 2, Fall: After Revelation (Box PF-2)
    - 1986
      - Quarterly West, No. 23: Morning Ablutions (excerpt from a novel) (Box PF-2)
      - The Montana Review, 8: Time Enough For the World, Vol. 8: January (Box PF-2)
      - Arete: The Journal of Sport Literature, Vol. III, No. 2, Spring: The Devil-Possum (Box PF-2)
      - The Georgia Review, Vol. XL, No. 1, Spring: The Snow That Is Nothing In the Triangle (Box PF-2)
      - New Mexico Humanities Review, Vol. 9, No. 2, Summer: Medal of Honor (Box PF-2)
    - 1987
      - Books and Religion, Vol. 15, No. 3 and 4, Mar./Apr.: Excerpt from I Am One of You Forever (Box PF-2)
      - Mid-Atlantic Country, Vol. VIII, No. 8, Aug.: The Overspill (Box PF-2)
      - Balcones, Vol. 1, No. 3, Fall: Say It Was Me (Box PF-2)
    - 1988
      - Crypt of Cthulhu, Vol. 7, No. 6: The Stain (Box PF-2)
      - Epoch, Vol. 37, No. 1: General Science (excerpt from a novel) (Box PF-2)
      - The Madison Review, Vol. 10, No. 2, Winter: O, Supreme Clairon (Box PF-2)
    - 1989
      - Chronicles Vol. 13, No. 5, May: Alien Worlds (Box PF-2)
      - Deathrealm, Issue 9, Summer: The Adder (Box PF-2)
      - Story, Autumn: The Devil-Possum (Box PF-2)
    - 1990
      - Deathrealm, Issue 11, Spring: Free Hand (Box PF-2)
      - Weird Tales, No. 298, Fall: Ember (Box PF-2)
    - 1991
      - Inverno Horror: Dagon (Box PF-2)
      - Chronicles, Vol. 15, No. 3, Mar.: Ancestors (Box PF-2)
      - The Sewanee Review, Vol. XCIX, No. 2, Summer: Detour (Box PF-2)
    - 1994
      - The Purple Monkey, Vol. 2, Issue 1, Spring: Better Things (Box PF-2)
    - 1996
      - Quarterly West, No. 42, Spring/Summer: The Helpinest Woman (Box PF-2)
      - Five Points, Vol. 1, No. 1, Fall: The Shooting Woman (Box PF-2)
      - Janus, No. 2, Winter: The Encyclopedia Daniel (Box PF-2)
    - 1997
      - Cold-drill: Say It Was Me (Box PF-2)
      - Now and Then: The Appalachian Magazine, Vol. 14, No. 1, Spring: Snakehandling (Box PF-2)
    - N.d.
      - The Brown Bag, Vol. 1, No. III: Homage to Plato (Box PF-2)
      - The Brown Bag, Vol. 1, No. V: Darkened Light (Box PF-2)
      - Long Pond Review, 3: The Overspill (Box PF-2)
  - Poetry Subseries, 1955-1997 and undated
    Serials containing poems by Chappell, arranged chronologically.
    - 1955 (Box PP-1)
      - The Archive, Vol. 68, No. 1, Oct.: In the Vault, Keep This in Mind (Box PP-1)
      - The Archive, Vol. 68, No. 2, Dec.: Song for a Demonlover's Suspicions, and Two Forms of Animal Faith (fiction) (Box PP-1)
    - 1956
      - The Archive, Vol. 68, No. 3, Feb.: Three Faces of Love. See Printed Material: Fiction Subseries, same date (Box PP-1)
    - 1959
      - The Archive, Vol. 72, No. 2, Dec.: Ode to Light (Box PP-1)
    - 1960
      - The Archive, Vol. 72, No. 3, Mar.: Familiar Poem (Box PP-1)
    - 1962
      - The Archive, Vol. 75, No. 1, Oct.: The Land of Cockayne, The Fevered Child, and My Son, Aged Two (Box PP-1)
    - 1963
      - Cockatrice, No. 4, Spring: Jim Applewhite Dreams in Springtime (Box PP-1)
    - 1965
      - Southern Poetry Review, Vol. V, No. 2, Spring: Marine (Box PP-1)
    - 1967
      - Carolina Quarterly, Vol. XIX, No. 2, Spring: The Naked Ark (Box PP-1)
    - 1968
      - The Above Ground Review, Vol. 1, No. 2, Nov.: The Survivors, Will and Testament of the Last Satiric Poet, The Poets Are Rattling Like Rusty, and Sottopasagio (Box PP-1)
      - The Brown Bag, July: The Farm (Box PP-1)
    - 1969
      - Clim, Vol. 1, No. 1: The Quick, Early Concert (Box PP-1)
      - The Dragonfly, No. 3, Fall: My Cough (Box PP-1)
    - 1970
      - Contempora, July/Aug.: The Sister Dying (Box PP-1)
      - The Above Ground Review, Vol. 2, No. 1, Summer: Skin Flick (Box PP-1)
      - Fly By Night: Gold and Mean (Box PP-1)
    - 1971
      - The Above Ground Review, Vol. 2, No. 3, Summer-Fall: Alphabet (Box PP-1)
      - The Brown Bag: Seated Figure (Box PP-1)
    - 1972
      - The Film Journal, Vol. 2, No. 1: Skin Flick (Box PP-1)
    - 1973
      - Counter / Measures: A Magazine of Rime, Meter, and Song, No. 2: A Sacred Head Now Wounded (Box PP-1)
      - Vol. XIII, No. 2, Spring: My Grandmother Washes Her Feet (Box PP-1)
      - The Film Journal, Vol. 2, No. 2: Caligari By Dreamlight (Box PP-1)
    - 1974
      - Southern Poetry Review, Vol. XIV, No. 1, Spring: My Grandfather Gets Doused (Box PP-1)
      - Three Rivers Poetry Journal, 3/4: The Last Rose of Summer (Box PP-1)
    - 1975
      - Appalachian Journal, Vol. 2, No. 2, Winter: Awakening to Music (Box PP-1)
      - Carolina Quarterly, Vol. XXVII, No. 1, Winter: Music as Natural Resource (Box PP-1)
      - Duke Alumni Register, Nov.: My Grandfather Gets Doused (Box PP-1)
      - North Carolina Poetry: The Seventies, Vol. XV: The Animal Dream (Box PP-1)
      - The Greensboro Sun: The Evening of the Second Day (Box PP-1)
      - Uwharrie Review, Vol. II, No. 1, Fall: Get Well Soon (Box PP-1)
    - 1976
      - Appalachian Heritage, Vol. 4, No. 2, Spring: My Father's Hurricane (Box PP-1)
      - Guilford Review, No. 4, Fall: Burning the Frankenstein Monster (Box PP-1)
      - Long Pond Review, Jan.: An American Suicide Speaks to the Asian Dead (Box PP-1)
      - Speak: Delayed by Mongol Forces at National Airport (Box PP-1)
    - 1977
      - Southern Poetry Review: The Seventies, Vol. 16: Bucket Stop (Box PP-1)
      - The Archive, Vol. 89, No. 2, Spring: Rimbaud Fire Letter to Jim Applewhite (Box PP-1)
      - Southern Poetry Review, Vol. XVII, No. 1, Spring: Beerdrinking in America (Box PP-1)
      - Southern Poetry Review, Vol. XVII, No. 2, Fall: Dawn Wind Unlocks the River Sky (Box PP-1)
      - The Little Review, Vol. 5, No. 4, Issue 12: My Father Burns Washington (Box PP-1)
      - The Sewanee Review, Vol. LXXXV, No. 3, Summer: Humility, Child in the Fog, and Transmogrification of the Diva (Box PP-1)
      - Quarterly West, No. 4, Autumn: The Highest Wind That Ever Blew: Homage to Lewis (Box PP-1)
      - Vanderbilt Poetry Review, Vol. 2, No. 3 & 4: Fire Now Wakening on the River (Box PP-1)
    - 1978
      - The Poetry Miscellany: Wind Subsides on the Earth River (Box PP-1)
      - Vanderbilt Poetry Review, Vol. III, No. 1 & 2: Firewood (Box PP-1)
      - Graffiti, No. 9, Spring: Three Sheets in the Wind (Box PP-1)
      - Tar Heel: The Magazine of North Carolina, Apr.: Mullein, Dodder, and Honeysuckle (Box PP-1)
      - Appalachian Journal, Vol. 6, No. 1, Autumn: My Mother Shoots the Breeze (Box PP-1)
      - Carolina Quarterly, Vol. XXX, No. 3, Fall: Remembering Wind Mountain at Sunset (Box PP-1)
      - The Davidson Miscellany, Fall: Fox and Geese (Box PP-1)
      - National Forum: The Phi Kappa Phi Journal, Vol. LVIII, No. 4, Fall: Chipmunk, Goldenrod, and Nettle (Box PP-1)
      - The Greensboro Sun, Vol. 6, Issue 2, Nov.: Common Creatures (Box PP-1)